<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Portfolio Website for Advait Jayant</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Portfolio Website for Advait Jayant</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:27:21 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>House Price Prediction</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog5/</guid>
      <description>Executive Summary A. Background Information B. Data Cleaning C. Exploratory Data Analysis D. Regression E. Diagnosis and Prediction  Background Information Let’s start this analysis with a bit of background information. As students of the world interested in traveling, we have heard about the Oktoberfest festival which takes place yearly in Munich. For this event, we are looking for accommodation and all of our friends have recommended us Airbnb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>House Price Prediction</title>
      <link>/projects/aliquam/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/projects/aliquam/</guid>
      <description>#Executive Summary
#Introduction
The Ames Housing dataset was compiled by Dean De Cock for use in data science education. It’s an incredible alternative for data scientists looking for a modernized and expanded version of the often cited Boston Housing dataset. Let’s say that we are looking to buy a house in Ames, Iowa, and we want to find the best possible house for our price range, so we are going to use different supervised machine learning techniques to actually find how much this property will set us back!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Munich Airbnb Price Prediction</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog1/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog1/</guid>
      <description>Executive Summary
 Background Information
 Data Cleaning
 Exploratory Data Analysis
 Regression
 Diagnosis and Prediction
  Background Information   Let’s start this analysis with a bit of background information. As students of the world interested in traveling, we have heard about the Oktoberfest festival which takes place yearly in Munich. For this event, we are looking for accommodation and all of our friends have recommended us Airbnb.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Netflix and Chill</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog4/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog4/</guid>
      <description>Analysing the IMDB Dataset   Now that we know our alcohol, we will now take a look at what bonds people even closer together - movies!!! In order to know about all the possible popular and good movies, we thankfully have IMDB, therefore, we will be using the IMDB 5000 dataset to perform our analysis.
Whenever approaching a problem statement, we need to make sure to use the IICE 4 step plan.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Approval Ratings</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog2/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog2/</guid>
      <description>Trump’s Approval Margins   Objective: The primary objective of this part of the challenge is to clearly find how Trump’s approval ratings fluctuated as a function of time (in weeks) throughout the past 4 years. Dataset Used: Five-Thirty-Eight.com (Trump-Approval Data)
Part-1: Reproducing the Plot Our end-goal is to be able to reproduce the following plot: Let us begin the project by importing the CSV file containing the data of the approval poll into our document.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Trump&#39;s Approval Ratings</title>
      <link>/blogs/blog3/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 31 Oct 2017 22:26:13 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/blogs/blog3/</guid>
      <description>Challenge 2: GDP components over time and among countries   Objective: In this challenge, we will look at how does the GDP and its components vary over time, and compare different countries. We will pay special attention to how much each component contributes to that country’s GDP.
What is the GDP exactly?
The GDP is the Gross Domestic Product, and its main components are: Personal Consumption (C), Business Investment (I), Government Spending (G), and Net Exports.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>